加分就對了
Aren't you somethin' to admire, cause your shine is somethin' like a mirror
你真是個令人傾慕的藝術品 你閃耀著光芒就像面閃亮的鏡子
And I can't help but notice, you reflect in this heart of mine
而且我真的無法不注意到 你的鏡面反映到我的心 撲通撲通地為你跳動
If you ever feel alone and the glare makes me hard to find
如果你感到寂寞 而且我剛好因為你的光芒太閃耀而讓我無法看清
Just know that I'm always parallel on the other side
記住這件事 我永遠都在鏡子的另一端平行著守候你
Cause with your hand in my hand and a pocket full of soul
因為只要我握著你的手 我們心神合一
I can tell you there's no place we couldn't go
去那裡都改變不了我們之間的真愛
Just put your hand on the past, I'm here tryin' to pull you through
你只要伸出你的手 我就會將你向我拉近
You just gotta be strong
女孩 我只要你好好地 堅強點
Cause I don't wanna lose you now
因為我不想要失去你
I'm lookin' right at the other half of me
我凝視著你，我的另一半
The vacancy that sat in my heart
我心中那片唯一的空位
Is a space that now you hold
就是唯有你能填滿的地方
Show me how to fight for now
告訴我 該怎麼持續我們的感情
And I'll tell you baby, it was easy
親愛的 我跟你說 我的方法很簡單 就是我愛你
Comin' back into you once I figured it out
我曾做錯過 但現在我知道唯有你才是我想要的
You were right here all along
你一直都在這兒守護我
It's like you're my mirror
就像是你是我的反映
My mirror staring back at me
我在鏡中的反映 我們凝視著彼此
I couldn't get any bigger
除了你之外
With anyone else beside of me
沒有任何人能讓我如此癡迷
And now it's clear as this promise
現在這一切更是清澈
That we're making two reflections into one
因為我們兩個反射 融合成一體
Cause it's like you're my mirror
就像是你是我在鏡子另一端的反映
My mirror staring back at me, staring back at me
互相凝視著 互相凝視
Aren't you somethin', an original, cause it doesn't seem merely assembled
你真是特別 不須特別雕飾 你就是你
And I can't help but stare cause I see truth somewhere in your eyes
我無法阻擋自己炙熱的視線 我在你眼中看見了真實
I can't ever change without you, you reflect me, I love that about you
沒了你 我沒辦法生活 你反映著我 我愛你這樣子映照著我
And if I could, I would look at us all the time
如果可以的話 我想看著我們兩人 那樣 我會看到我倆相容吧
Cause with your hand in my hand and a pocket full of soul
因為只要我握著你的手 我們心神合一
I can tell you there's no place we couldn't go
去那裡都改變不了我們之間的真愛
Just put your hand on the past, I'm here tryin' to pull you through
你只要伸出你的手 我就會將你向我拉近
You just gotta be strong
女孩 我只要你好好地 堅強點
Cause I don't wanna lose you now
因為我不想要失去你
I'm lookin' right at the other half of me
我凝視著你，我的另一半
The vacancy that sat in my heart
我心中那片唯一的空位
Is a space that now you hold
就是唯有你能填滿的地方
Show me how to fight for now
告訴我 該怎麼持續我們的感情
And I'll tell you baby, it was easy
親愛的 我跟你說 我的方法很簡單 就是我愛你
Comin' back into you once I figured it out
我曾做錯過 但現在我知道唯有你才是我想要的
You were right here all along
你一直都在這兒守護我
It's like you're my mirror
就像是你是我的反映
My mirror staring back at me
我在鏡中的反映 我們凝視著彼此
I couldn't get any bigger
除了你之外
With anyone else beside of me
沒有任何人能讓我更加深陷難出
And now it's clear as this promise
現在這一切更是清澈
That we're making two reflections into one
因為我們兩個反射 融合成一體
Cause it's like you're my mirror
就像是你是我在鏡子另一端的反映
My mirror staring back at me, staring back at me
互相凝視著 互相凝視
Yesterday is history
昨天已成過去
Tomorrow's a mystery
明日無法預測
I can see you lookin' back at me
我知道你和我相互照看著
Keep your eyes on me
讓你的目光停留在我身上
Baby, keep your eyes on me
寶貝 別移開你的目光
Cause I don't wanna lose you now
因為我不想要失去你
I'm lookin' right at the other half of me
我凝視著你，我的另一半
The vacancy that sat in my heart
我心中那片唯一的空位
Is a space that now you hold
就是唯有你能填滿的地方
Show me how to fight for now
告訴我 該怎麼持續我們的感情
And I'll tell you baby, it was easy
親愛的 我跟你說 我的方法很簡單 就是我愛你
Comin' back into you once I figured it out
我曾做錯過 但現在我知道唯有你才是我想要的
You were right here all along
你一直都在這兒守護我
It's like you're my mirror
就像是你是我的反映
My mirror staring back at me
我在鏡中的反映 我們凝視著彼此
I couldn't get any bigger
除了你之外
With anyone else beside of me
沒有任何人能讓我更加深陷難出
And now it's clear as this promise
現在這一切更是清澈
That we're making two reflections into one
因為我們兩個反射 融合成一體
And now it's clear as this promise
現在這一切更是清澈
That we're making two reflections into one
因為我們兩個反射 融合成一體
Cause it's like you're my mirror
就像是你是我在鏡子另一端的反映
My mirror staring back at me, staring back at me
互相凝視著 互相凝視
You are you are the love of my life (x10)
你是我此生的真愛 就是你 (x10)
Baby you're the inspiration for this precious song
寶貝 你就是這首珍貴的歌的靈感來源
And I just wanna see your face light up since you put me on
我只是想看到你聽到這首歌時臉上閃耀的光芒
So now I say goodbye to the old me, it's already gone
現在 我和過去搞砸的那個我道別 他已經不在了
And I can't wait wait wait wait wait to get you home
我等不急要和你和在一起
Just to let you know, you are
對了 以防你不知道 你是──
You are you are the love of my life (x8)
你是我此生的真愛 (x8)
Girl you're my reflection, all I see is you
女孩 你是我的另一半 我眼中只有你
My reflection, in everything I do
不論我做什麼 你都在那兒當我的反射著我
You're my reflection and all I see is you
你是我的另一半 我眼中只有你
My reflection, in everything I do
不論我做什麼 你都在那兒反射著我
You are you are the love of my life (x16)
你是我此生的真愛 (x16)